const localTalentHardQuestions = [
  {
    id: 24,
    question: 'The numbers at the beginning of a piece of music represent the:',
    answers: ['Beat', 'Time signature', 'Notes'],
    correct: 'Time signature',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: 'How many notes are in a major scale?',
    answers: ['6', '8', '7'],
    correct: '7',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: 'Which of these means “very quiet”?',
    answers: ['pp', 'Lente', 'Quieto'],
    correct: 'pp',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: 'What term is used to “play loudly”?',
    answers: ['Piano', 'Forte', 'Staccato'],
    correct: 'Forte',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: 'What is the term for a gradual increase in volume?',
    answers: ['Descendo', 'Forte', 'Crescendo'],
    correct: 'Crescendo',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: 'What is the opposite of Staccato?',
    answers: ['Allegro', 'Andante', 'Legato'],
    correct: 'Legato',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: 'How many notes separate an octave?',
    answers: ['10', '6', '8'],
    correct: '8',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: 'How many different notes are in a pentatonic scale?',
    answers: ['7', '5', '8'],
    correct: '5',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: 'What is the note name of the 4th fret on the B string?',
    answers: ['C', 'D#', 'E'],
    correct: 'D#',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 53,
    question: 'What is a semitone?',
    answers: [
      'A half step/The distance from one fret to the next',
      'A full step/The distance from one fret to the next',
      'A quarter step/The distance between two frets',
    ],
    correct: 'A half step/The distance from one fret to the next',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question: 'What is the Relative minor of B?',
    answers: ['G', 'Bm', 'G# Minor'],
    correct: 'G# Minor',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question:
      'Where do you see if a note is marked as sharp for an entire composition?',
    answers: [
      'Next to the time signature',
      'In the staff',
      'Before the treble clef',
    ],
    correct: 'Next to the time signature',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: 'What symbol indicates Slide down in Tablature?',
    answers: ['/', '\\', '<'],
    correct: '/',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: 'What is a Capotasto?',
    answers: [
      'A capo',
      'A term to say “get louder”',
      'A term to say “play staccato',
    ],
    correct: 'A capo',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question: 'What is an arpeggio?',
    answers: [
      'A chord strummed all at once',
      'A scale',
      'A broken up chord played consecutively',
    ],
    correct: 'A broken up chord played consecutively',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'hard',
    reward: 3,
  },
]

export { localTalentHardQuestions }
